Kevin Reid

289-688-8896 | kevinnivek@me.com | linkedin.com/in/kevinreidkr/ | Oshawa, ON_ **Portfolio:** https://vinyldude8896.github.io/portfolio_react/

About Me

I am a Web Developer who has recently completed a Full Stack Web Development bootcamp, and with a 2-year diploma in Object Oriented Programming. I am looking for a full-time role with a desire to grow and develop my technical skills. I excel in roles with multiple projects requiring analytical and development skills.

My goal in development is to earn experience and build solutions that meet stakeholder requirements following best industry practices with a strong customer focus.

My experience is based in Warehouse Logistics Management, Distribution Center Leadership, IT Support, and Customer Escalations. I have excelled in these roles by striving to make data-driven process improvements.

Technical Skills

Front End: ReactJS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery, Responsive CSS, HTML

Application: Node.js, Visual Basic, Java, Express **Database:** MySQL, Mongo DB, GraphQL, IndexedDB

Tools: Git Management, Visual Studio, local

Power Platform Fundamentals Certification

Education

University of Toronto Certificate Program in Full Stack Web Development	Apr 2023 – Oct 2023 Toronto, ON
Advanced Business Technologies 2 Year program in Object Oriented Programming	Jan 1999 – Jan 2001 Saint John, NB
Udemy WordPress Development, Advanced React Development	Mar 2023 – Present
Microsoft Learn	June 2023 – Present

Related Projects

Pagination project: Incorporated pagination into existing codebase.

GitHub: https://github.com/Vinyldude8896/Blog_Pagination

Deployed Project: https://blogpagination.herokuapp.com

iBetter: Full stack application with secure login

GitHub: https://github.com/Vinyldude8896/iBetter **Deployed Project:** https://ibetter.herokuapp.com/

Tech Blog: Full stack application blog site

GitHub: https://github.com/Vinyldude8896/The-Tech-Blog **Deployed Project:** https://immense-cliffs-94479.herokuapp.com

Weather: Weather app with conditions and forecast

GitHub: https://github.com/Vinyldude8896/Weather-Dashboard

Deployed Project: https://vinyldude8896.github.io/Weather-Dashboard/

Employment History

H&M (Hennes Mauritz Inc) Distribution Center Team Lead

Jun 2023 – Current Ajax, ON

Leading a large team of associates and support staff to pick store replenishment and allocation inventory as well as all online Canadian orders. Working closely with shipping and packing departments to ensure the appropriate amount of work is being assigned for the day.

Amazon Delivery Process Assistant/Assistant Manager

Nov 2021 - June 2023

Whitby, ON

Collaborating with various teams to ensure the highest level of delivery success. Increased delivery success rate, decreased parcels not on van, decreased customer escalations over a significant period by implementing new data sources and reporting tools.

Amazon Delivery Delivery Station Liaison

May 2021 - Nov 2021 Whitby, ON

Collaborating with third-party vendors and station staff to resolve customer escalations and missed deliveries. Created a reporting and logging tool resulting in a significant increase in productivity, increase in overall success rates and a decrease in individual and team call time.